(Leonard:)and craziness
going on...
No, you told me.
(Leonard:)Okay, um...
(Leonard:)Well, there was this girl.
(Penny:)What did you do?
Nothing...
(Amy:)really.
(Leonard:)It was just kissing.
(Penny:)And then what?
And then nothing.
(Leonard:)I stopped it.
(Leonard:)But it still bothers me, and...
(Leonard:)I wanted you to know.
(sighs)
(Emily:)All right.
(Leonard:)Did you ever do anything
like this since we've been...?
(Penny:)Nope, never.
Oh, that's too bad.
(Sheldon:)You know,
can I ask you a question?
Hmm?
(Penny:)Why are you
telling me this now?
(Leonard:)Well, like I said,
we're about to get married,
and I-I want a clean slate.
(Leonard:)No secrets.
(Amy:)Really?
Be-Because to me,
(Penny:)it seems like
we're about to get married
(Penny:)and you're trying
to sabotage it.
W-Would you rather
I didn't tell you?
(Penny:)No, I don't want there
to be secrets between us.
See, now I'm confused.